{
    "id": "403c0eb524e64486a78d515f2d2b8e66",
    "title": "Gap Fills Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I ……………………… sure that she is lying.",
            "description": "When feel is used to talk about reactions and opinions, it is not normally used in the continuous form.",
            "answers": [
                "feel",
                "am feeling",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "They are ……………………… kind people!",
            "description": "In exclamations, we use such before an adjective + plural noun.",
            "answers": [
                "such",
                "so"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "That was ……………………….. kind of you.",
            "description": "So is used before an adjective.",
            "answers": [
                "such",
                "so"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I ………………………. him to arrive at 3 o’clock.",
            "description": "Before an object, wait and hope are followed by for.",
            "answers": [
                "expect",
                "hope",
                "wait"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "You should never steal someone ……………………….. ideas.",
            "description": "Else has a possessive form – else’s.",
            "answers": [
                "else",
                "else's"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "She was ………………………. anxious.",
            "description": "Too is not used with much before an adjective.",
            "answers": [
                "too",
                "too much",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I am completely ………………………….",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "exhausted",
                "exhausting"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I have difficulty ……………………………. dates.",
            "description": "Difficulty is followed by (in) + ing form.",
            "answers": [
                "to remember",
                "remembering",
                "in remembering"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "The whole village was ……………………….. water.",
            "description": "We use under when something is covered by what is over it.",
            "answers": [
                "below",
                "under"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I didn’t like this jacket ………………………., it is too large.",
            "description": "Besides means in addition.",
            "answers": [
                "beside",
                "besides"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "How do you …………………………. the vacuum cleaner?",
            "description": "We make machines start.",
            "answers": [
                "begin",
                "start",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "If my grandmother had been alive, she ……………………….. 95 this year.",
            "description": "In the third conditional, we use a past perfect tense in the if-clause and would have + past participle in the main clause. ",
            "answers": [
                "will be",
                "would be",
                "would have been"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        }
    ]
}